

Carlos Sebastian Fernandez Front End Developer



Portfolio: https://carlos-fernandez.netlify.app/

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Sass, SQL, MySQL, Git, GitHub, Figma.

Studying right now: ReactJs, Angular

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

Intermediate/ English -Advanced

HOBBIES

- Travel
- **Sports**
- Video Games
- Movies & Series

PROFILE

Currently looking for a front end development position where I could put in practice all my skills and gain experience at the same time.

I am a creative and curious person, and I like facing new challenges.

EXPERIENCE

CSFwebs Since 01/22

https://csfwebs.com/

This is my main project as Web Developer. I started offering my services of designing and development of websites for people all around the world.

2014 - 2022 **Evil Bastards BMX**

2016 - 2017

Buenos Aires, Lomas de Zamora

My first job. Here I spent my days doing administrative tasks. Such us stock control, products, prices updating & billing.

Scientific South Foundation

Buenos Aires, Lomas de Zamora

Internship done in my last year of High School. It was a period where I was working as administrative trainee. (documents management, customer service, etc).

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development 04/22 - 12/22 Buenos Aires, Argentina

Numen Academy

Front End Development 2021 - 2022

Buenos Aires, Argentina SoloLearn Community

2012 - 2017 Bachelor E&A (economy and administration)

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Sacred Heart of Jesus College, High School



+54 11 2254-8711

Csfernandez00@gmail.com

Argentina, Buenos Aires

Last Update 06/07/2022



Carlos Sebastian Fernandez Desarrollador Front End



Portafolio: https://carlos-fernandez.netlify.app/

Conocimientos

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Sass, SQL, MySQL, Git, GitHub, Figma.

Actalmente estudiando: ReactJs, Angular

Idiomas

Español - Nativo

Intermedio/ Ingles Avanzado

HOBBIES

- Viajar
- Deportes
- Video juegos
- Peliculas y Series

PERFIL

Actualmente me encuentro en la busqueda de un puesto como desarrollador Front End para poder aportar mis conocimientos a un equipo de trabajo, crecer como professional y ganar experiencia laboral.

Inicio 01/22

2014 - 2022

2016 - 2017

04/22 - 12/22

2012 - 2017

Soy una persona creativa, curiosa y que le gustan los nuevos desafios.

EXPERIENCIA

CSFwebs

https://csfwebs.com/

Periodo de trabajo como freelancer de desarrollo web. encargado del diseño y maquetado de sitios web a pedido de los clientes.

Evil Bastards BMX

Buenos Aires. Lomas de Zamora

Puesto de trabajo administrativo, donde realizaba tareas de control de stock, armado de pedidos, despacho de productos, actualizacion de listas de precios y facturacion tanto de clientes como de proveedores.

Fundacion Cientifica del Sur

Buenos Aires, Lomas de Zamora

Pasantia realizada en mi ultimo año de secundaria donde me encargaba de realizar tareas administrativas, atencion al cliente y manejo de archivos y documentacion.

FORMACION

Diplomatura en Desarrollo Web Full Stack

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Academia Numen

Desarrollo Front End 2021 - 2022

Buenos Aires, Argentina **SoloLearn Community**

Bachiller en Economia y Administracion

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Colegio Sagrado Corazon de Jesus



+54 11 2254-8711





Actualizado al 06/07/2022